name: 'Possessive Adjectives'
questions:
  -
    question: 'I''m English. $ name is William.'
    answers:
      - Your
      - Our
      - My
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'We''re from Russia. $ names are Anton and Masha.'
    answers:
      - Our
      - Your
      - My
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'A: What''s $ name?\nI''m Tom. Nice to meet you.'
    answers:
      - our
      - my
      - your
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'He''s American. $ name is Nick.'
    answers:
      - My
      - His
      - Your
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'We''re Mexican. $ names are Martha and Antonio.'
    answers:
      - My
      - Their
      - Our
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'That''s their cat. $ name is Diamond.'
    answers:
      - His
      - Its
      - Her
    correct: 2
  -
    question: '$ name is Tina. She''s Brazilian.'
    answers:
      - Her
      - His
      - Your
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'A: We''re Jane and Justin Thomas.\nB: Romm 34. This is $ key.'
    answers:
      - my
      - our
      - your
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I''m Kate, and this is $ dog, Rover.'
    answers:
      - my
      - our
      - your
    correct: 1
  -
    question: "A: It's $ bag!\nB: No, your bag's there."
    answers:
      - your
      - my
      - our
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'They''re British. $ names are Brian and Naomi.'
    answers:
      - my
      - their
      - our
    correct: 2
